Man, today was crazy.
Feels like I lived a full week in one day.
What? Why? How?
What possessed Himari to do that?!
It was so out of left field,
my emotions can hardly keep up!
Times like these call for flowers.
You think Himari kissed me
cause she likes me like that?
How the hell am I supposed to
act around Hima—
Hey Natsu.
Having fun talking
to flowers all by yourself?
Can a Boy-Girl Friendship Survive?
(No, It Can't!!)
I know you're plotting
behind my back with Kureha-san.
Goodbye, Sunflower
Huh? Nope, I don't know anything about that.
I'm not involved this time.
You're not?
Well, I tried.
But she used me for info
and tossed me aside.
I guess she prefers to work alone.
Then why didn't you
convince her to let Hima—
I can't do that!
You still want Himari to go to Tokyo, huh?
Not exactly.
Huh?
I'd never turn my back on Kureha-san.
Because I love her.
Got a problem with that?
I can fall in love too, you know!
N-Never mind that!
What about you?
N-Nothing much.
Come on!
After everything I just told you?
What's this about smooching Himari-chan?
I-I-I don't remember telling you that!
Technically, you didn't.
I'd be more careful talking to flowers.
So? Did you confess?
No... We went to the Sunflower Festival.
She kept mentioning Enomoto-san,
when she suddenly...
So that's how.
This is perfect!
I figured I had no role to play this time,
but this changes everything!
You seem to be having lots of fun.
Either way, I doubt you
can act like friends now.
I-I guess not.
Then I suggest you focus
on the task at hand.
See ya.
Makishima's right.
If I lose this battle,
I'd have to give up Himari.
There's only one thing I can do now.
Focus on making my masterpiece, like always!
Look at all these delicious
dumplings I made for everyone.
Lemme dive in first on this
springy sandwich of goodness.
Here I go!
Yum, yum.
Yum, yum, yum.
Yummy, yummy.
Yummy, yummy, yum, yum, yum...
Did that happen?
What have I done?
Oh my gosh!
It's not a dream?
Please, let it be a dream!
Why did I do that?!
How can I even message him?
What do I even say?
"Which is more springy?"
"Dumplings or my lips?"
Shut up, you idiot!
What kind of high school girl says that?!
He hates me. I know it.
Himari? Can I come in?
It's Onii-chan!
I can't let him find out!
Going somewhere?
I see.
You were annoyed by his
wishy-washy attitude,
so you kissed him on impulse.
Oh well. What's done is done.
You thought I would scold you?
You deserve praise
for being true to your feelings.
Besides, if you get dumped,
I can swoop in to save the day!
So no worries!
I totally forgot. He lives for this stuff.
Well, time for me to eat dinner.
I noticed the smell of delicious dumplings.
R-Right, Onii-chan...
About the dumplings...
The hell is this?!
There isn't a single one left!
I'm sorry!
Science Room
I can't tell.
They might be done. They might not.
Ever since yesterday,
I keep thinking of Himari.
I can't focus.
Yu-kun, what's up?
Enomoto-san! Don't you have practice?
I decided to come by for lunch.
It's lunch time already?
Were you about to take these out?
I'm not sure yet.
Even if it looks done on the surface,
it might still have
coloring left in the center.
If it's not done all the way,
it could cause problems later on.
Oh, are these the ones
you got with Hii-chan?
Y-Yup.
You picked them out while you kissed?
Actually, we picked them out
and then we kiss—
Makishima told you, huh?
Yup. Darn. I wish I went.
I wouldn't have let Hii-chan get ahead.
I'm not sure how to respond to that.
Listen, Enomoto-san.
I think I need to tell Himari how I feel.
Good for you.
You think so?
To me, it makes no difference
whether you two go out.
Even if you were dating from the start,
I would have told you how I felt.
Oh yeah, that's how she is.
I'm gonna be Hii-chan's number one friend.
Maybe one day, she'll agree
to share you with me.
That's my end goal!
I'll get back to practice.
See ya later.
H-Hey, um... I...
Punishment!
Himari! You okay?!
She was for real that time!
I was about to die!
L-Look, Himari.
I'm not gonna pretend like
yesterday didn't happen.
So... um...
There's something I need to tell you
after I beat Kureha-san!
Sure.
Okay, now what?
I didn't think about how to act
after saying that!
I need a diversion!
I think it's about the right time...
Oh well, here goes nothing!
What do you plan to make with these?
A sunflower tiara.
That sounds amazing!
Her smile was even cuter than that time...
before my middle school exhibit.
You're gonna be gone for the Obon holidays?
Yup.
We're going on a family trip
while my dad's back home.
Oh... How about you, Enomoto-san?
I have to help out at the store.
Our cakes sell out during Obon.
It's the busy season, then.
I can't work at home
with my older sisters visiting.
But school's closed during break.
I gotta figure out a workspace.
Why don't you use our place then?
I'll let Onii-chan know.
For real? Thanks!
Three more days until the match.
Wow, Yu-kun.
You worked so hard.
Your tiara's great.
Kureha-kun won't stand a chance.
Thank you.
Finally, you'll get to
be my little brother for real.
Let's say cheers
with the tiara to celebrate!
I showed you yesterday too, though.
It's so good, I can't get enough!
Yu-kun, what happened?
What's going on?
How did this happen?
The flowers are dying
from losing their inner moisture.
Did I mess up the timing back then?
Can this be fixed somehow?
No, not at this point.
I can tidy up how it looks
but not the quality.
Any spares?
I was so focused on making just one.
I used them all up in trial runs.
Yu-kun, I'll grab the car.
Let's go look for sunflowers.
We'll search stores across the city—
Hibari-san.
You've been drinking.
There.
Yu-kun, I'm coming in.
Good morning.
Morning...
It's been a while since I had some
quality Yu time. Put me right to sleep.
I needed that to rejuvenate
myself after my trip.
You say that like I'm a beauty treatment.
Seems like trouble broke out
while I was gone.
Sorry.
Let's see the final product!
Right!
Wow! It's so cute!
Don't you think Onii-chan?
I think it's a good piece.
I'm proud of you for bouncing back
in a matter of a few days.
Can I go ahead and take a look?
Please.
Wow, it's so cute!
It looks much better
than the ones on social media.
Is this a wedding tiara?
The sunflowers are so bold.
What a fashion statement.
I like the attention to detail, too.
You really think so?
Yup! It's definitely cute.
I actually want it for myself.
You mean I won the matc—
Hmm, I dunno about that.
It's cute, but not good enough!
But you just said you want it!
Were you planning on saying that either way?
I'd never do something that unfair.
If you actually made something good,
I was planning on giving up Himari-chan.
Then why?
It's obvious, isn't it?
You were supposed to give
it your all in this match.
But you tried to play it off
with a failed piece.
And I'm being unfair?
That's not true.
I always put my all into every piec—
Then why did you bring me a back-up piece?
I heard about the flowers dying.
Sakura-chan told me so.
You tried to trick me.
Why didn't you tell me the truth?
But if I could just make it in time—
If you did, then what?
You said he was your best creator.
What a waste of time.
All right, Rion! Let's go home.
I should say hi to mom for a change.
You have something to say?
Why did you tell Kureha-san
about the flowers dying?
What were you about
to tell Kureha back there?
Let me guess.
"If I could just make it
in time, it'd be fine."
If you're not serious about
accessories, give it up already.
Saku-nee-san, you're saying
I'm not serious about it?
You remember these?
The returned pieces...
When I spoke with Sasaki-sensei,
he was very understanding.
Other than one thing:
the quality of the pieces.
What do you mean?
Take a closer look.
There's two more with the same issue.
And another one with a cracked petal.
You understand what this means?
Remember when I said your pieces
were frozen in time?
Yeah...
Until then, you'd never sold
a defective product.
But after I told you that,
you've made four bad pieces.
Your past work showed
that you gave it your all.
But all it took was a little play on
romance to get you off your game.
You're not cut out to be a creator.
You couldn't even get serious
for this match with your dream at stake.
Get your head straight
if you really want to be a creator.
Keep customers out of it
if you're going to prioritize romance.
Feel ashamed for toying around
with this ridiculous tiara in a dire match.
Hey, Yu...
Himari.
About what I said before I made this tiara.
Sorry. Forget I said anything.
Himari.
Let's go.
What did you bring me out here for?
Sorry, but I don't plan
on going to Tokyo like you want.
You heard from Natsu, right?
I'm not involved in this one.
My plans start from here.
Himari-chan.
Join Kureha-san's agency
and aim for the top.
Excuse me? I told you
my promise with Yu comes first.
I know that's not easy to say,
especially with finances.
Isn't that more of a reason
to accept Kureha-san's offer?
What do you mean?
It's the perfect opportunity
to get your name out there.
All the more if you want to
promote Natsu's accessories.
Your strength is your charm.
Go learn how to best
leverage those strengths.
Accepting Kureha-san's offer
is only your ticket.
B-But I have to support Yu.
Rin-chan can do that.
Still!
I'm not telling you to hand him over.
Just to let her borrow him.
If your bond's the real deal,
a few years apart can't hurt.
The real deal?
How about this?
One day, when you two's dream comes true,
and you still feel
the same way towards Natsu,
I promise to help you
with everything I've got.
I might be a player,
but I can keep a promise.
Think about it.
It's my fault for drowning in romance
and throwing aside friendship.
All while Yu was serious about his work.
I was the one who screwed everything up.
Is this the last time
I get to cling onto you?
Kinda makes you think, doesn't it?
It's hot enough as it is. Get off.
Don't cheat on me while I'm gone, okay?
Who's cheating? We're not even dating.
Don't say that like you're
not crazy for me.
You didn't even accept
an offer from Enocchi.
By the way, Himari.
You're not gonna "Bwa-ha!" at me today?
Feels like one of those
crossroads in life, doesn't it?
If I become a famous model,
I can promote your accessories even more.
Which means our dream will come true.
Maybe, yeah.
Or I could beg my grandpa
to pay off my debt.
Which means we could live out our cute,
raunchy high school dreams!
Don't say it like that!
That's an awful way to put it.
Our future dream or our romance today.
Which one are we supposed to live for?
Himari, don't forget.
If you want me to give up my dream—
J-Jeez, Yu. You're so obsessed with flowers.
No, I'm willing to—
It's all you care about, I get it.
Himari!
Please.
I can't bear you quitting.
I can't.
This world is full of contradictions.
Betting on our future together
is probably the right thing to do.
But for that, we have no
choice but to be apart.
It's messed up, but I'll accept it.
Somewhere down this path,
we'll meet again one day.
Even if our love looks different by then,
I believe we'll still laugh together.
As best friends.
Farewell to our romance.
I wish you well.
Flowers that Bloom Along
the Path of Dreams